(Leonard:)Right, sorry. Sorry.
- And stop apologizing all the time.
- Right. Sorry.
(Penny:)All right, let's shoot stuff.
Do you want me
to show you what to do?
I play a lot of "Grand Theft Auto."
I think I know how to handle a gat.
(Penny:)Wow, you are cute
when you get all gangsta.
(Leonard:)So I've got a gunshot wound.
(Leonard:)That's pretty badass.
(Penny:)No, you've got a Reebok
with a gunshot wound...
...and an ouchie on your pinky toe.
(Leonard:)Hello? They gave me a Band-Aid.
(Leonard:)Hospitals do not issue Band-Aids unless
it is medically necessary. That is the law.
(Penny:)Well, thank you for a really cool evening.
(Leonard:)Thank you for hiding my Star Wars
socks at the emergency room.